AYUSH JAMES

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER



linkedin.com/in/ayushjames



github.com/iwishjames



ayushpjames@gmail.com



0401 379 011

PROFILE

I am a Junior Developer who is committed to creating tasteful web applications, by considering the experience of the users, and the objectives of the product - form and function.

I believe my educational and employment experiences enable me to meet the demand for developers with both technical knowledge and business acumen.

I take pride in knowing that that a career in software best positions me to make a valuable contribution to humanity's technological advancements. I am excited for what is to come!

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Immersive

2019

General Assembly, Sydney

2017

University of Wollongong

Bachelor of Commerce (Accounting)

RECENT PROJECTS

Fire Dash - Bushfire information Dashboard

REACT, CSS ANIMATIONS, XML/JSON DATA

A centralised dashboard with information on weather, fire ratings and tweets from RFS and BOM. github.com/iwishjames/fire-dash

Locus - Sydney suburb guide

RUBY ON RAILS, GOOGLE MAPS API, JAVASCRIPT

[Group Project] A centralised guide for renters that provides a breakdown of the property market in Sydney. github.com/lpinzari/project-suburb

XP - GA student forum

RUBY ON RAILS, BOOTSTRAP, HEROKU

A community forum and knowledge base consisting of tips and experiences shared from the General Assembly. github.com/iwishjames/project1

EXPERIENCE

AR Media

Mar 2019 - Dec 2019

Creative

Role: Applying creative approaches to marketing and presenting social media content.

Transferable Skills: Marketing strategy, social marketing,

Publift (AdTech)

Sep 2018 - Jun 2019

Accounts Manager

Role: Ad revenue processing and management

Transferable Skills: Business acumen, user experience, project management, client-relationship management

Deloitte (Assurance Advisory)

Apr 2018 - Sep 2018

Junior Analyst

Role: Big-4 bank remediation project.

Transferable Skills: Team collaboration, task management.

Prime Partners (Business Advisory) Nov 2017 - Apr 2018

Graduate Accountant

Role: Assisting with tax and business advisory for individuals. Transferable Skills: Process documentation, emotional intelligence.